A Guide to Records of the Secretary of Commerce and Trade, 1995-2010 (bulk 2006-2009)
Library of Virginia
- Series VII: Secretary's Correspondence, 2006-2009., Extent: 13 boxes. (Box 53-63, 66-67)
  - Jamestown 2007 Steering Committee, 2007. (Box 60, Folder 2)
  - Governor's Working Group on the Taxation of Machinery and Tools, 2007. (Box 60, Folder 3)
  - Motorcycle Advisory Council, 2008. (Box 60, Folder 4)
  - NGA Mission Growth Working Group, 2008. (Box 60, Folder 5)
  - NGA Policy Academy, 2008. (Box 60, Folder 6)
  - Secure Commonwealth Panel, 2006-2009. (Box 60, Folder 7-10)
  - Joint Commission on Technology and Science Aerospace Advisory Committee, 2007. (Box 60, Folder 11)
  - Urban Policy Task Force, 2006-2007. (Box 60, Folder 12)
  - Virginia Institute of Government Advisory Council, 2007-2008. (Box 61, Folder 1)
  - Virginia Institute of Marine Science (VIMS), 2006. (Box 61, Folder 2)
  - Virginia Israel Advisory Board, 2006-2008. (Box 61, Folder 3)
  - Viginia Manufacturing Advisory Council, 2006-2008. (Box 61, Folder 4)
  - Virginia Manufacturing and Development Commission, 2006-2009. (Box 61, Folder 5-10)
  - Virginia Modeling and Simulation Advisory Council, 2006-2009. (Box 61, Folder 11)
  - Virginia National Defense Industrial Authority (VNDIA), 2006-2009. (Box 62, Folder 1-8)
  - Virginia's Philpott Manufacturing Extension Partnership (VPMEP), 2006-2009. (Box 62, Folder 9-11)
  - VRTAC (Virginia Research and Technology Advisory Commission), 2006-2007. (Box 62, Folder 12)
  - Virginia Sesquicentnnial of American Civil War Commission, 2007-2009. (Box 62, Folder 13)
  - Virginia Workforce Council (VWC), 2005-2010. (Box 63, Folder 1-10)
  - Sec. Gottschalk Chrono. Files, Jan. 2006-Dec. 2007 (Box 66, Folder 1-12)
  - Attorney General's Office, 2006-2009. (Box 67, Folder 1)
  - Constituents (General), 2006-2009. (Box 67, Folder 2)
  - Freedom of Information Act (FOIA), 2006-2009. (Box 67, Folder 3)
  - Commerce and Trade FOIA (Freedom of Information), 2008. (Box 67, Folder 4)
  - General Correspondence, 2006-2009. (Box 67, Folder 5-11)
  - Secretary of Agriculture and Forestry, 2006-2009. (Box 67, Folder 12)
  - Commonwealth Preparedness (VA Critical Infrastructure Protection and Resiliency Strategic Plan), 2008. (Box 67, Folder 13)
  - Secretary of Education, 2006-2008. (Box 67, Folder 14)
  - Secretary of Health and Human Resources, 2006-2009. (Box 67, Folder 15)
  - Secretary of Public Safety, 2008. (Box 67, Folder 16)
  - Secretary of Technology, 2006-2007. (Box 67, Folder 17)
  - Secretary of Transportation, 2006-2009. (Box 67, Folder 18)
  - Sec. of Transportation--Transportation Partnership, 2007-2008. (Box 67, Folder 19-20)
- Series VIII: Files, 2006-2009., Extent: 16 boxes. (Box 64-65, 68-69, 79-90)
  - Budget Files, 2006. (Box 64, Folder 1-9)
  - Budget Files, 2007-2010. (Box 65, Folder 1-12)
  - Agency Employees on Temporary Assignment, 2006-2009. (Box 68, Folder 1)
  - CT Misc. Admin. Matters, 2007-2008. (Box 68, Folder 2)
  - SOCT Agency At-Wills, 2007. (Box 68, Folder 3)
  - Commerce and Trade Agency Head Retreats 2007-2008. (Box 68, Folder 4-7)
  - Commerce and Trade Continuity of Government Plan, 2007. (Box 68, Folder 8)
  - Gift Log, 2006-2009. (Box 68, Folder 9-12)
  - Commerce and Trade Monthly Financial Statements, 2006-2009. (Box 68, Folder 13)
  - Commerce and Trade Major Projects and Initiatives, 2007-2008. (Box 68, Folder 14)
  - SOCT VA Perfomers Website - State Agency Performance Measures, 2006-2007. (Box 68, Folder 15)
  - Weekly Reports, 2006-2009. (Box 68, Folder 16-21)
  - Commonwealth of VA - Report of the Comptroller (Fiscal Year Ended June 30, 2006), 2006-2008. (Box 69)
  - Report on Statewide Financial Management and Compliance (Quarterly) - Office of the Comptroller, 2005-2008. (Box 69)
  - Cabinet Meetings, 2006-2008 (Box 79)
  - SOCT Agency Head Meeting With Governor, 2007. (Box 79)
  - Virginia Congressional Delegation Briefings, 2006-2009. (Box 79)
  - Legislative Files, 2006. (Box 80)
  - Legislative Files, 2006-2007. (Box 81)
  - Legislative Files, 2007. (Box 82)
  - Legislative Files, 2007. (Box 83)
  - Legislative Files, 2007. (Box 84)
  - Legislative Files, 2007-2008. (Box 85)
  - Legislative Files, 2009. (Box 86)
  - Legislative Files, 2007-2009. (Box 87)
  - Legislative Files, 2009. (Box 88)
  - Regulatory Records, Feb. 2006-Dec. 2007. (Box 89)
  - Regulatory Records, Nov. 2007-Jan. 2010. (Box 90)
- Series IX: Economic Development Organizations, 2006-2009., Extent: 5 boxes. (Box 73-77)
  - Artech, Inc., 2009. (Box 73, Folder 1)
  - Amerigroup Corporation, 2009. (Box 73, Folder 2)
  - AOL LLC, 2007. (Box 73, Folder 3)
  - Asian Pacific American Business Resource Guide, 2006. (Box 73, Folder 4)
  - Bluefield College, n.d. (Box 73, Folder 5)
  - Blue Ridge Crossroads, n.d. (Box 73, Folder 6)
  - City of Bristol, Virginia, 2007. (Box 73, Folder 7)
  - Canada, 2007. (Box 73, Folder 8)
  - Capital Outlay Progress, 2007-2009. (Box 73, Folder 9)
  - Carroll County, n.d. (Box 73, Folder 10)
  - Center for Applied Innovation (CAI), 2006. (Box 73, Folder 11)
  - Center for Employment Training, 2006. (Box 73, Folder 12)
  - Center for Homeland Security and Defense, 2005. (Box 73, Folder 13)
  - Center for Rural Virginia-Council for Rural Virginia, 2007. (Box 73, Folder 14)
  - CGI/AMS Northrup Grumman, n.d. (Box 73, Folder 15)
  - Chesapeake Bioscience Education Foundation, 2008. (Box 73, Folder 16)
  - Chesapeake Crescent, 2009. (Box 73, Folder 17)
  - Chesterfield County, 2009. (Box 73, Folder 18)
  - Comcast, 2007. (Box 73, Folder 19)
  - Commonwealth Homeland Security Foundation, 2009. (Box 73, Folder 20)
  - Community College Workforce Alliance, 2006-2009. (Box 73, Folder 21)
  - Council on Virginia's Future, 2005-2006. (Box 73, Folder 22)
  - Council on the Americas, 2008. (Box 73, Folder 23)
  - Danville, 2006. (Box 73, Folder 24)
  - Department of Defense, 2005. (Box 73, Folder 25)
  - Dominion Power, 2006-2007. (Box 73, Folder 26)
  - Emergency Preparedness, 2006. (Box 73, Folder 27)
  - Governor's Ethanol Coalition, 2008. (Box 73, Folder 28)
  - Fairfax County Economic Development Authority, 2008. (Box 73, Folder 29)
  - Department of Forestry, 2008. (Box 73, Folder 30)
  - George Mason University, 2006-2008. (Box 73, Folder 31)
  - Goodwill Industries, 2008. (Box 73, Folder 32)
  - Greater Richmond Partnership, Inc., 2006. (Box 73, Folder 33)
  - Greater Washington Initiative, 2008-2009. (Box 73, Folder 34)
  - Hallowed Ground, 2006. (Box 73, Folder 35)
  - Hampton Roads Bridge-Tunnel Expansion Feasibility Study, 2008. (Box 73, Folder 36)
  - Hampton Roads Economic Development Alliance, 2008. (Box 73, Folder 37)
  - Hampton Roads Military & Federal Facilities Alliance (HRMFFA), 2007-2009. (Box 73, Folder 38)
  - Hampton Roads Partnership, 2007-2009. (Box 73, Folder 39)
  - Hampton Roads Planning District Commission, 2006. (Box 73, Folder 40)
  - Hampton Roads Research Partnership, 2008. (Box 73, Folder 41)
  - City of Harrisonburg, 2008. (Box 73, Folder 42)
  - Homeland Security, 2007. (Box 73, Folder 43)
  - Homeland Security Council (HSC), 2006. (Box 73, Folder 44)
  - Institute for Defense and Homeland Security (IDHS), 2006. (Box 73, Folder 45)
  - Israel, 2009. (Box 73, Folder 46)
  - Jamestown 2007, 2006-2007. (Box 73, Folder 47)
  - Jefferson Lab (Thomas Jefferson National Accelerator Facility), 2007. (Box 73, Folder 48)
  - Jewish Community Federation of Richmond, 2008. (Box 73, Folder 49)
  - Journey Through Hallowed Ground, 2007-2009. (Box 73, Folder 50)
  - Korea (Peace City), 2006. (Box 74, Folder 1)
  - Lenowisco Planning District Commission, 2007. (Box 74, Folder 2)
  - LG&E Energy, LLC (Filing-Federal Energy Regulatory Commission), 2006. (Box 74, Folder 3)
  - LISC Virginia (Local Initiatives Support Corporation), 2006. (Box 74, Folder 4)
  - Maersk, Inc., 2008. (Box 74, Folder 5)
  - Marine Corps Heritage Foundation, 2007. (Box 74, Folder 6)
  - Market Street Services, 2006. (Box 74, Folder 7)
  - Mecklenburg County, 2009. (Box 74, Folder 8)
  - Metropolitan Washington Airports Authority, 2006. (Box 74, Folder 9)
  - Microsoft, 2006. (Box 74, Folder 10)
  - Department of Minority Business Enterprise (DMBE), 2006. (Box 74, Folder 11)
  - Miscellaneous (The Dixie Group, Incorporated), 2006. (Box 74, Folder 12)
  - Modeling and Stimulation, 2006-2009. (Box 74, Folder 13)
  - Moton Museum, 2009. (Box 74, Folder 14)
  - NASA, 2006-2007. (Box 74, Folder 15)
  - NASA Langley, 2006. (Box 74, Folder 16)
  - National Association of Manufacturers, 2006. (Box 74, Folder 17)
  - NC State University, 2007. (Box 74, Folder 18)
  - New River Valley Economic Development Alliance, 2007. (Box 74, Folder 19)
  - New River Valley Planning District Commission, 2008. (Box 74, Folder 20)
  - Norfolk, n.d. (Box 74, Folder 21)
  - Norfolk Cruise Ship Program, 2006. (Box 74, Folder 22)
  - Northrup Grumman Newport News Shipbuilding, 2008. (Box 74, Folder 23)
  - Northrup Grumman Newport News Tour of Facility, 2006. (Box 74, Folder 24)
  - Old Dominion Electric Cooperative, 2008. (Box 74, Folder 25)
  - Old Dominion University, 2006-2009. (Box 74, Folder 26)
  - Virginia Board for People with Disabilities, 2007-2008. (Box 74, Folder 27-28)
  - Pittsylvania County (Berry Hill Road Development - Mega Park), 2009. (Box 74, Folder 29)
  - Poplar Hill Project, Farmville, 2006. (Box 74, Folder 30)
  - Poquoson, City of, 2008. (Box 74, Folder 31)
  - Potomac Field Gear--Buchanan County, 2006. (Box 74, Folder 32)
  - The Power of Green, by Thomas L. Friedman, 2007. (Box 74, Folder 33)
  - Preservation Virginia, 2009. (Box 74, Folder 34)
  - Post-Katrina Preparedness, 2006. (Box 74, Folder 35)
  - Related Affordable Housing (Tiki Barber), 2008. (Box 75, Folder 1)
  - Richmond, City of--Economic Development, n.d. (Box 75, Folder 2)
  - Virginia Rural Caucus, 2007. (Box 75, Folder 3)
  - Russell County, 2009. (Box 75, Folder 4)
  - Russell County Proposal to Cumberland Plateau Company (Garden Side Village at Lebanon), 2006. (Box 75, Folder 5-6)
  - Virginia Seafood Council, 2008-2009. (Box 75, Folder 7)
  - Seawind Renewable Energy Corporation (VA Offshore Wind Energy Project), 2009. (Box 75, Folder 8)
  - Southeast Rural Community Assistance Project, Inc., 2007. (Box 75, Folder 9)
  - Start Strong Initiative, n.d. (Box 75, Folder 10)
  - State Corporation Commission - Dominion Coal Plant Proceeding (Wise County), 2007. (Box 75, Folder 11)
  - Suntrust Bank, 2006. (Box 75, Folder 12)
  - Sussex County (Groundwater Withdrawal Permit Renewal), 2008-2009. (Box 75, Folder 13)
  - Virginia Sustainable Building Network, 2008. (Box 75, Folder 14)
  - SWaM Procurement Plan, 2006. (Box 75, Folder 15)
  - SWAM (Small, Women and Minority Owned Business), 2006. (Box 75, Folder 16)
  - Southeast RCAP (Southeast Rural Community Assistance Project), 2006-2007. (Box 75, Folder 17)
  - Textron, Inc., 2008. (Box 75, Folder 18)
  - Thomas Jefferson Foundation, Inc., 2008. (Box 75, Folder 19)
  - Thomas Jefferson Partnership For Economic Development Inc., 2007. (Box 75, Folder 20)
  - U-Haul International, Inc., 2008. (Box 75, Folder 21)
  - Uniform Accident Prevention and Safety Program, 2005-2008. (Box 75, Folder 22)
  - University of Virginia, 2007-2009 (Box 75, Folder 23)
  - The Uriah Group (Gordon Meriwether), n.d. (Box 75, Folder 24)
  - Vint Hill Economic Development Authority, 2007. (Box 76, Folder 25)
  - Virginia Arts Festival, 2007. (Box 76, Folder 2)
  - Virginia Business Excellence Consortium, 2008. (Box 76, Folder 3)
  - Virginia Chamber of Commerce, 2008-2009. (Box 76, Folder 4)
  - Virginia College of Osteopathic Medicine, 2007. (Box 76, Folder 5)
  - Virginia Coalfield Economic Development Authority, 2007. (Box 76, Folder 6)
  - VCU 2006 Virginia Executive Institute Program, 2006-2007. (Box 76, Folder 7)
  - Virginia Commonwealth University (VCU), 2007-2009. (Box 76, Folder 8)
  - Virginia Community College System, 2006-2008. (Box 76, Folder 9)
  - Virginia Economic Developers Association (VEDA), 2006-2009. (Box 76, Folder 10)
  - Virginia Food Policy Council, 2007. (Box 76, Folder 11)
  - Virginia Forestry Assoc. Annual Convention, 2006. (Box 76, Folder 12)
  - Virginia Golf Council, 2007. (Box 76, Folder 13)
  - Virginia Manufacturers Association (VMA), 2007. (Box 76, Folder 14)
  - Virginia Microelectronics Consortium (VMEC), 2008. (Box 76, Folder 15)
  - Virginia Military Advisory Council (VMAC), n.d. (Box 76, Folder 16)
  - Virginia Museum of Natural History, 2006. (Box 76, Folder 17)
  - Virginia Port Authority, 2007-2009. (Box 76, Folder 18)
  - Virginia School Boards Association (VSBA), 2008. (Box 76, Folder 19)
  - Virginia State Police, 2005-2008. (Box 76, Folder 20)
  - Virginia Wireless Service Authorities Act, 2009. (Box 76, Folder 21)
  - Virginia Tech, 2005-2007. (Box 76, Folder 22)
  - VITA (Virginia Information Technologies Agency), 2006-2009. (Box 76, Folder 23-24)
  - Wallops Island - Wallops Research Parking Taxiway, 2006-2009. (Box 76, Folder 25)
  - Washington Communities, LLC, 2007. (Box 76, Folder 26)
  - Washington County, Virginia, 2008. (Box 76, Folder 27)
  - Washington Dulles-Tel Aviv Route, 2009. (Box 76, Folder 28)
  - William and Mary College, 2007. (Box 76, Folder 29)
  - Virginia Economic Bridge Inc., 2006-2008. (Box 77, Folder 1-4)
  - I-73 Location Study - Final Environmental Impact Study, Vol 1, 2006. (Box 77, Folder 5-6)
  - I-73 Location Study - Final Environmental Impact Study, Vol 2, 2006. (Box 77, Folder 7-8)
- Series X: Warner Administration Records,., Extent: 9 boxes. (Box 95-103)
  - VRTAC, 2002-2005. (Box 95, Folder 1-3)
  - Virginia Biotechnology Research Authority, 1998-2005. (Box 95, Folder 4-7)
  - VA Commercial space Flight Authority, 2004-2005. (Box 95, Folder 8)
  - Mars Plan, 2004. (Box 95, Folder 9)
  - MD/VA Spaceport, 2002-2003. (Box 95, Folder 10-11)
  - Wallops Island, 2002-2003. (Box 95, Folder 12)
  - VA Commercial Space Flight Authority, 1999-2004. (Box 95, Folder 13-15)
  - Virginia Israel Advisory Board, 2001-2005. (Box 95, Folder 16)
  - VIMS, 2003-2005. (Box 96, Folder 1-2)
  - VIMSIM, 2005. (Box 96, Folder 3-9)
  - VIMSIM Budget, 2005. (Box 96, Folder 10)
  - SWAM, 2002-2005. (Box 97, Folder 1-4)
  - C&T--DMBE SWAM, 2002-2005. (Box 97, Folder 5)
  - VPMEP, 1995-2006. (Box 97, Folder 6-9)
  - VPMEP Study, 2005. (Box 97, Folder 10)
  - Council on Virginia's Future, 2003-2005. (Box 98, Folder 1-6)
  - Langley Research Center, 1998-2002. (Box 98, Folder 7)
  - Manufacturing Intiatives--Council Nominees, 2005. (Box 98, Folder 8)
  - Manufacturing Summitt II, 2005. (Box 98, Folder 9)
  - Manufacturing, 2004-2005. (Box 98, Folder 10)
  - VA Manufacturing Advisory Council, 2004-2005. (Box 98, Folder 11)
  - Advanced Manufacturing Intiative, 2003-2005. (Box 98, Folder 12)
  - Manufacturing, 2004. (Box 98, Folder 13)
  - IEDC (International Economic Development Council), 2004. (Box 98, Folder 14)
  - Manufacturing Iniatiative, 2003-2004. (Box 98, Folder 15)
  - Manufacturing Extension Service, 2003. (Box 98, Folder 16)
  - Modeling and Simulation, 2005. (Box 99, Folder 1-3)
  - Motorsports Valley, 2001-2005. (Box 99, Folder 4-10)
  - Bristol Motor Speedway, 2004. (Box 99, Folder 11)
  - Nextel, 2003. (Box 99, Folder 12)
  - Offshore Gas, 2005. (Box 99, Folder 13)
  - HJR 625 Meeting, 2002. (Box 99, Folder 14)
  - Offshore Gas, 2005. (Box 99, Folder 15-16)
  - Race to GED, 2003-2005. (Box 99, Folder 17-18)
  - RAISE Initiative, 2005. (Box 99, Folder 19)
  - Virginia Works, 2001-2005. (Box 100, Folder 1-5)
  - Workforce Initiative, 2002-2005. (Box 100, Folder 6-11)
  - Virginia Works Implementation, 2005. (Box 101, Folder 1-2)
  - Jobs for Virginia, 2004. (Box 101, Folder 3)
  - Virginia Works Implementation, 2005. (Box 101, Folder 4)
  - Virginia Works, 2003-2005. (Box 101, Folder 5-10)
  - Jobs for Virginia, 2004. (Box 101, Folder 11)
  - Virginia Works, 2004. (Box 101, Folder 12)
  - Base Realignment and Closure Commission (BRAC), 2002-2005. (Box 102, Folder 1-14)
  - Virginia Workforce Council, 2005. (Box 103, Folder 1)
  - Workforce and Econ. Dev., 2005. (Box 103, Folder 2)
  - Workforce Iniatiative Proposal, 2002-2003. (Box 103, Folder 3)
  - BRAC, 2005-2006. (Box 103, Folder 4)
  - CGI-AMS, 2005. (Box 103, Folder 5)
  - Center for Innovative Technology, 2002-2005. (Box 103, Folder 6-8)